[{"answer": "Hey Veronica.  You look terrible", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Geez, thanks", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Hey Veronica.  You look terrible", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " No, I didnt mean it like that.  I just mean you look so tired.  Are you OK", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Geez, thanks", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Yeah, Im fine.  I just pulled an all-nighter last night", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": " No, I didnt mean it like that.  I just mean you look so tired.  Are you OK", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Were you cramming for a test or something", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Yeah, Im fine.  I just pulled an all-nighter last night", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " No.  I had a paper due in one of my classes today and I worked on it all night", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Were you cramming for a test or something", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Oh, what class", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 19, "question": " No.  I had a paper due in one of my classes today and I worked on it all night", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Spanish lit", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Oh, what class", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Ooh.  I bet that was tough.  Did you finish", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Spanish lit", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Yeah. I got it finished, but its not very good", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Ooh.  I bet that was tough.  Did you finish", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Well, at least you finished.  Im sure its a good paper", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Yeah. I got it finished, but its not very good", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Thanks", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Well, at least you finished.  Im sure its a good paper", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " So, are you ready for final exams", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Thanks", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " No.  Please, dont remind me!  I have to start studying", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 29, "question": " So, are you ready for final exams", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Me too.  How many do you have", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 30, "question": " No.  Please, dont remind me!  I have to start studying", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Lets see  I have one for all of my classes except World History", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Me too.  How many do you have", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": "How come you dont have a final in that one", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Lets see  I have one for all of my classes except World History", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " We just have a final paper to submit instead of an exam. Thats somethin", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 33, "question": "How come you dont have a final in that one", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " I know.  I hate the end of the term.  They give us so much work at once", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 37, "question": " We just have a final paper to submit instead of an exam. Thats somethin", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Tell me about it", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I know.  I hate the end of the term.  They give us so much work at once", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " So, have you started studying for our Biology exam", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Tell me about it", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " No.  Not yet.  Have you", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 40, "question": " So, have you started studying for our Biology exam", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " No.  Want to study together?  I think a few other people from class are going t", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 41, "question": " No.  Not yet.  Have you", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Sure.  When are you guys meeting", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 45, "question": " No.  Want to study together?  I think a few other people from class are going t", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " I think were going to meet Sunday at 1 at the library.  Were going to reserve ", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Sure.  When are you guys meeting", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " That sounds good.  How are you going to prepare for the exam", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 50, "question": " I think were going to meet Sunday at 1 at the library.  Were going to reserve ", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Im not sure yet.  Do you have any ideas", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 51, "question": " That sounds good.  How are you going to prepare for the exam", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Well, I was thinking of reviewing my notes and making note cards with all o", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Im not sure yet.  Do you have any ideas", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Thats a good idea.  We have a lot of vocabulary to memorize", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Well, I was thinking of reviewing my notes and making note cards with all o", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " I know", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Thats a good idea.  We have a lot of vocabulary to memorize", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Jake from class has a copy of last years exam too.  So, maybe that will help us", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 58, "question": " I know", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Whered he get that", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Jake from class has a copy of last years exam too.  So, maybe that will help us", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " His brother is a year older and took the class last year", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Whered he get that", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Cool!  At least that will give us an idea of the format of the exam", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 64, "question": " His brother is a year older and took the class last year", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Yeah.  The questions will be different this year, Im sure.  But, we can get a", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Cool!  At least that will give us an idea of the format of the exam", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Hopefully it wont be too hard", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Yeah.  The questions will be different this year, Im sure.  But, we can get a", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " I think that as long as we study, well be ok.  Do you want to study by ourselve", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Hopefully it wont be too hard", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Lets do that", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 74, "question": " I think that as long as we study, well be ok.  Do you want to study by ourselve", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Ok.  Well, Ill see you Sunday and we can plan the rest then", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Lets do that", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " OK.  See you later", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Ok.  Well, Ill see you Sunday and we can plan the rest then", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Bye!  Get some rest", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " OK.  See you later", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Thanks", "docId": "06-06", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Bye!  Get some rest", "qSentId": 77}]
